militaryoneclick.com 2016-10-29

# 

                                    Website Privacy Policy
The management and staff of MilitaryOneClick are committed to maintaining
the confidentiality of non-public, personal information we collect from
individuals who visit our website. We want you to understand how and why we
collect, use and disclose the personal information about you on our website.
This Website Privacy Policy ("Policy") provides you with information concerning
our practices and procedures as they relate specifically to information we
collect at this website. If you have additional questions or would like further
information on this topic, please feel free to write to us at
support@militaryoneclick.com. We may update this Policy from time to time, so
please check this Policy periodically for changes. This Privacy Policy applies to
this website and does not apply to any other products or services or to
information collected in any other way (whether offline or online) by
MilitaryOneClick or its partnering entities.
Personal Information We Collect and Use at this Website
When you request information, subscribe to a mailing list or for a service or respond to an online
survey, we may collect your personal information. We define “personal information” as
information that is unique to you and might include your name, e-mail address(es), mailing
address(es), telephone number and certain information related to the business you represent such
as number of employees and industry type. If you encounter a screen or page that requests
information you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed
with that screen or page. If your personal information is required in order to allow us to respond
to your inquiry, you will receive a notice advising you of this. In each such instance, you will
know what personal information we collect through the website, because you actively submit it.
If you do provide us with personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described
where it is collected, and we will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of
MilitaryOneClick or its partnering entities unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so, (2) it is
necessary to allow our service providers, partnering entities or agents to provide services for us
or for you, (3) in order to provide our products or services or those of our partnering entities to
you, (4) it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other
entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements, (5) it is necessary in connection with a
sale of all or substantially all of the assets of MilitaryOneClick or the merger of
MilitaryOneClick into another entity or any consolidation, equity exchange, combination,
reorganization, or like transaction in which MilitaryOneClick is not the survivor, or (6) otherwise
as we are required or permitted by law.
If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your
information (whether collected online or offline) with third parties for their
marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as
indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section of this Policy.
Email
~#4845-1898-6253 v.1~

We appreciate your questions and comments about our website and services
and welcome your email messages to mailboxes listed on our website. We will
share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable
of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of
your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We
may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your
email address will not be used for any other purpose.
Confidentiality and Security Measures
We restrict access to personal information collected about you at our website to
our employees or others who need to know that information to provide services
to you or in the course of conducting our normal business operations. While no
website can guarantee security, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic,
and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information collected via
the website. We protect our databases with various physical, technical and
procedural measures and we restrict access to your information by
unauthorized persons. We also advise all MilitaryOneClick employees about
their responsibility to protect customer data and we provide them with
appropriate guidelines for adhering to our company's business ethics standards
and confidentiality policies.
We respect our current and former customers' privacy and we value your
business.
Use of "Cookies" or Other Data Collection Tools
A cookie is a piece of information which a web server may place on your
computer when you visit a website. Cookies are commonly used by websites to
improve the user experience and have not been known to transmit computer
viruses or otherwise harm your computer. Many cookies last only through a
single website session, or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may
remain on your computer until you delete them.
We may use cookies for a number of purposes - for example, to maintain
continuity during a user session, to gather data about the usage of our website
for research and other purposes, to store your preferences for certain kinds of
information and marketing offers, or to store a user name or encrypted
identification number so that you do not have to provide this information every
time you return to our website.
Our cookies will track only your activity relating to your online activity on this
website, and will not track your other Internet activity. Our cookies do not
gather personally identifiable information.
You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring
your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject
cookies, you may not be able to use certain of our online products and services
or website features.
~#4845-1898-6253 v.1~

We may occasionally use other companies to set cookies on our website and
gather cookie information for us. In some cases, we may also use another
company to operate web servers for our website.                         We use the cookie
information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated above.
In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we also obtain information which you
provide to us online - for example, when you sign up for product updates or when you purchase
products or otherwise communicate with us. In some cases, we retain both the cookie
information and/or the information you provide to us online - for example, to complete a
transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases,
we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for
your use in subsequent sessions.
Certain pages on our websites contain "web beacons" (also know as Internet
tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain
information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page
on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon
appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of
browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third
party.
An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to
identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our website, we may
view the IP address (which may include the city, domain address and service provider) of the
device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general
physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our website
visitors come. We also may use this information to enhance our website.
Opt-Out
In connection with promotions or other projects, we may ask you specifically
whether you have objections with respect to a certain kind of data use or
sharing. If you opt-out under such circumstances, we will respect your decision.
To opt out of receiving commercial communications, please click on the "opt-
out" or "unsubscribe" link in the communication or please contact us at
support@militaryoneclick.com. Your e-mail address will be removed from our
marketing list. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy
your request, as some promotions may already be in process.
Access
If personal information you have submitted through the website is no longer
accurate, current, or complete, and you wish to update it, please send an e-
mail to support@militaryoneclick.com. Upon appropriate request we will usually
be glad to update or amend your information, but we reserve the right to use
information obtained previously to verify your identity or take other actions that
we believe are appropriate and lawful.
~#4845-1898-6253 v.1~

Email
We appreciate your questions and comments about our website and services
and welcome your email messages to mailboxes listed on our website. We will
share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable
of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of
your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We
may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your
email address will not be used for any other purpose.
Links to other Websites
For your convenience we may provide links to other websites and web pages that we do not
control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites or pages not under
our control and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products
described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or
pages.
Visiting our Site from Outside of the United States
If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, please be aware that your information
may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our central database is
operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not
be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect
your privacy.
Changes to Our Website Privacy Policy
We may change this Policy at any time and from time to time. The most recent version of the
Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Policy. This Policy is not
intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect
privacy, please write to us at support@militaryoneclick.com.
Last Updated: October 31, 2011
~#4845-1898-6253 v.1~
